

+44(0)758 543 1346 hong1015.github.io/Portfolio hongwong1015@gmail.com

PROFILE

My name is Hong, I've been working as a Lead Frontend developer at ZPG since 2016. As time goes on I have faced many challenges and learnt how to overcome them. I have gain extensive experience in building websites and solving many common problems that occur.

I am experienced at HTML, CSS, jQuery and JavaScript as well as basic React, Angular and Backend languages like C#, Razor and .NET. I work well under pressure and always use any spare time to improve myself by developing new

SKILLS

Html
CSS (LESS)
JavaScript & JQuery
SQL, C# and React
PHP
3D Modeling
2D & 3D Animation
Videos Editing
Photography

Softwares

Visual Studio, TSF
Microsoft SQL Server
Photoshop
Illustrator
InDesign
Premier Pro
3D Studio Max, Unity
Blender
ZBrush

EDUCATION

Anglia Ruskin University (2009 - 2012)
BSc (Hons) Multimedia, Animation and the Web 2:1

The Colne Community School and College A level (2007-2009)

Economics, Information & Communications Technology, AS Chinese, AS Art & Design 8 GCSE's (2002–2007)

Working history

ZPG (December 2016 - Present) | Lead Frontend developer -

Create, modify and maintain templates and bespoke websites.

Create HTML email.

Troubleshoot existing websites.

Working with outsource resource in and out of the UK, with website styling and function issues.

Experience working with Razor, Knockout.js, ASP.NET, VB.NET and C# based website. Using SQL for delete or update client database.

Assisting my manger in his absence with work allocation and general management of the development team of 6.

Technicweb (January 2015 - December 2016) | Frontend developer -

Modify and maintain templates.

Troubleshoot existing websites.

Experience working with Razor, Knockout.js, ASP.NET, VB.NET and C# based website.

Simonleedesign (July 2014) | Freelance web developer

Website development and image retouching

SeymourPowell (May 2014 – Jun 2014) | Freelance web developer Responsive website development

Two Wheels Rider Magazine (Sep 2013) | Freelance logo designer Logo design

2C Company Limited (March 2013 – August 2013) | Junior marketing officer Graphical drawing and design task in the office.

Computer market research.

Assists in retail shops, answering customer questions and setting up computers.

Exhibitor at Hong Kong computer & communications festival 2013.

Pacific Union Consultants Ltd. (Jun 2013) | Freelance logo designer Logo design

Additional information

I am a British Citizen, I can speak, read and write fluent Cantonese, Traditional Chinese and English.

My interests are Boxercise, Kick boxing, Basketball, Brazilian Jiu-jitsu and Jiu jitsu, I was also the university Jiu jitsu club treasurer, website maintainer and part of my role was to help at the university fresher's fair to recruit new members for the club. I am trustworthy, hardworking and self-motivated. My spare time hobbies are gaming, watching movies, exercise, landscape photography, table tennis, catching up with new design trends and learning new skills.